=Born Again=
=Episode 7=
You're awake?
You...
I'll make you pay back double
for what I suffered today.
You refused to sacrifice for art, right?
It's okay.
I'll help you.
Can't take it already?
How about this?
Director!
- You promised me.
- Mei, are you crazy?
As long as Xiaotang obeys,
you won't hurt her.
- Let go!
- No!
Mei, are you out of your mind?
How dare you stop me?
What's wrong with you?
Look at me! You want me to let her go?
Mei!
Say something. Say it.
Director Li, even at this point,
are you still going to hide the truth?
Qiang, your wife fell ill last month.
Can you afford her surgery?
Director Li said
he'd give you the marketing funds.
Did you get that money?
- Gu Xiaotang, what did you say?
- Director Li.
How did she know that?
You said that money...
She's lying. Don't trust her.
Right, Director Li wouldn't lie to us.
What are you doing?
Hu,
why are you still defending him?
Your brother got injured
on the construction site last year.
Did you get the compensation?
Director Li said
they had powerful connections
and promised to negotiate for you.
But if I remember correctly,
you're getting dismissed
next week, right?
Shut up, or you'll pay.
If you don't trust me, check his phone.
He's written
your dismissal letter on it.
Let me check your phone.
- Let me check.
- Wait, no phone on me.
- Give me the money.
- Give it to me.
- Let go!
- Give me the money.
The money for my wife.
Wait.
- I have no phone on me.
- Give me the money.
- What are you doing? Stop!
Give me the money.
Xiaotang, run!
Where's your conscience?
- Give me.
- She's getting away.
Get her!
Stop!
Run now! Run!
Go!
Mei, just go.
No, Xiaotang. It's all my fault.
I'll hold them off. Don't worry.
They won't hurt me.
Mei!
How dare you!
(Is everything going
to start all over again?)
Back up now!
What about Mei?
Let's get out first.
You remember the loop thing?
No.
Then why are you here?
I saw you touching your ear.
I remember you only do that
when you're upset.
I...
Since you were Xiaotang's classmate,
why not come work for me?
Xiaotang is always good to her friends.
Can you tell me more about
what you mentioned today?
About what?
The loop.
So, that's pretty much
how the loop works.
Did I talk too fast?
Did you get it?
Yes.
So if it weren't for the loop,
you wouldn't even remember me.
I remember you. You're Ye Shen.
That's not the point.
The point is,
the loop reset earlier this time.
That means, many things
would happen all over again.
If what you said is true,
and everything
will happen all over again,
we have to do something to stop it.
I can't drag you into this.
This has nothing to do with you.
I can handle it on my own.
Didn't you say we're allies?
Since we're allies,
and this isn't over yet,
we
can keep going.
Xiaotang, I have a new T-shirt for you.
It might not fit you well.
I'll put it right here.
Give it to me.
Then I'll step out.
Wait, could you help dry my hair?
My arm got hurt.
I can't lift it up.
Me?
Okay.
Done.
I'll go back now.
Wait.
Your
heart is beating fast.
Are you okay?
Are you scared of me?
I-I'm not.
Do you know that in the last loop,
we were way closer than this?
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
In the last loop,
we fought side by side.
And...
We even kissed.
Were you dreaming?
You don't believe it?
Am I the only one who remembers that?
Was it really not a dream?
Then tell me if this is a dream.
♪The face deep in the heart♪
♪Suddenly clear and hazy♪
♪Across time and space, eyes meet again♪
♪Deeply trapped in the vortex♪
♪Searching for familiar outlines♪
♪Persistently guarding,
endlessly cycling♪
♪Even for just a second♪
♪If raindrops flow backward
into the sky♪
♪And sunlight reverses♪
♪As the sun rises and sets,
we reunite with yesterday♪
♪I'll build a dream with you♪
♪Upon the ruins, spring breeze arrives♪
♪Even if there's no end,
I won't regret the start♪
♪Eternity like a day, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to recognize my eyes♪
♪Following the tracks
of the days that were♪
♪A day like a lifetime, rushing to you♪
♪You don't need to remember my name♪
♪I'll be the dawn you haven't seen♪